<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dispatch riders on demand</title>
    <link>https://ukuul.com/tags/about/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dispatch riders on demand</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://ukuul.com/tags/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://ukuul.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 02:28:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ukuul.com/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;about&#34;&gt;About&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://ukuul.com/img/baba.png&#34; class=&#34;img-responsive&#34; alt=&#34;Baba Coolio&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are you a small business owner, manager or sophisticated individual?
It&amp;rsquo;s likely you have delivery errands. Sending stuff, receiving stuff&amp;hellip; sound familiar?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you spend most of your time picking up or delivering items around town? ☹️&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you have a dispatch rider or 2 you call to run your errands?
How reliable are they? How do you know where your package is or when it has been delivered?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are you thinking of purchasing a motorcycle to run your deliveries/errands?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Delivery errands are a necessary evil. However, there is a better way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ukuul is a mobile app that allows anyone to send a dispatch rider on delivery errands. Deliveries can be simple or complicated. Enter your details and the app instantly gives you a quote. Ukuul provides predictable and empowering pricing based on distance. So whether you want to send a letter across town or deliver hair products to your customers. Ukuul is for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our dedicated dispatch service takes care of calling contacts and keeping tabs on your delivery. Even though we monitor your delivery, we allow you to do the same. The Ukuul app let&amp;rsquo;s you know exactly where your rider is. You get instant push notifications when packages are picked and delivered. Say goodbye to stressful deliveries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experience the future of delivery, today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beta testing in Accra.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Available on &lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ukuul.delivery&#34;&gt;Android&lt;/a&gt;. Coming soon to iPhone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;get-in-touch&#34;&gt;Get in Touch&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hotline:&lt;/strong&gt; 0561516300.
&lt;strong&gt;Email:&lt;/strong&gt; hello@ukuul.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>